A slightly more beautiful body
少 し美しい体を
please show me.
見 せてください
Please show me your skin.
肌を見せてください
Oh, wonderful.
ああ、素晴らしい
Ah, okay.
あ、いいです
That's fine.
いいです
Ah, I'll go.
あ、行っちゃうよ
quickly.
早く
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
It's gone.
出 てしまった
出てしまったね
Ah, a lot came out.
あ、いっぱい出てしまったね
I guess that's what it is.
なんか、あれなんだよね
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Oops, it's gone again.
おっと、また出ちゃった
I practiced again.
また、練習しちゃった
Wow, I almost did it.
すげえ、すげえかけちゃった
I put something on.
何かかけちゃったよ
I guess I'll take a shower at once.
一回でシャワーしようかね
I want to see you taking a shower.
シャワーしてるとこ見たいからさ
Just wash it like you normally would.
普段、普段みたいな洗い方でさ
yes.
はい
I wonder how I usually wash my clothes.
普段の、普段、どんな感じで洗っているのかなみたいな
Normally.
普通に
Sushi hurts.
お寿司痛いね
tits.
おっぱい
From my chest.
胸から
I guess I don't know.
一応、分かんないんだよね
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
There's nothing to touch here.
こっちはさ、触るところがつけないから
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだね
The style is really outstanding.
本当にスタイルは抜群だね
Ah, that's often said.
ああ、よく言われます
Did you wipe it?
拭けた?
Yes, I was able to wipe it.
はい、拭けました
Did you wipe it?
拭 け た?
yes,
はい、
I was able to wipe it.
拭 けました